[classical music playing over radio]
[engine revving]
[Jerry] This is a 1956 Chevrolet Corvette
convertible in cascade green,
with beige coves and interior.
It’s a pretty rare color,
only 290 were made.
It has a 265-cubic inch,
240 horsepower V-8.
Its got whitewall tires.
A two-speed Powerglide
automatic transmission.
Signal seeking AM radio.
It is absolutely the essence
of American futuristic positivism
of the post-war society at that time.
In the 1950s, people just didn’t see
anything that was bad.
Everything, from the American perspective,
looked like this car.
Colorful, energetic, happy...
"We’ve perfected life."
They couldn’t have been more wrong,
of course, but still.
I thought this would be perfect...
That car is you.
...for my special guest this week.
This is great.
[Jerry] The irrepressibly enjoyable host
of NBC’s Tonight Show, Mr. Jimmy Fallon.
When you’re around Jimmy,
you’re having a good time.
I don’t care who you are.
[cell phone ringing]
-[Jimmy] Hello?
-[Jerry] Jimmy?
-[Jimmy] This it?
-[Jerry] We’re gonna get coffee.
The talk show that comes to your house
and picks you up.
Hi, I’m Jerry Seinfeld,
and this is
Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee.
[engine revving]
[brake squeaks]
What car just makes you smile
and want to have fun?
An aqua ’56 Vette.
-That’s a beautiful thing.
-It’s beautiful.
This is just gorgeous, and the color.
What happened with cars?
Where did they stop making
colors like this?
Why did people
-stop having fun. Why?
-Stop having fun. Why?
In the larger sense of life.
Why did people stop having fun?
Why did they stop buying trampolines?
That’s a fantastic thing.
Everybody used to have them in the '50s.
-Oh, my God.
-[engine revving]
Are you kidding me? [laughing]
Car’s good, I’m good. Car’s bad, I’m bad.
That’s the way I live.
‘Cause I’m a car guy.
[Jimmy] This is it, we’re moving.
This is great. Oh, this feels good.
This is...
It doesn’t even feel like a convertible.
I know. It feels like a set.
-Like a spaceship.
-Yeah.
It feels like we’re on the set
and it’s just like a fake screen
next to you.
-Right?
-Right.
And next to you.
It doesn’t feel like the real thing.
-This is a Quentin Tarantino movie.
-Yeah.
I wish I had a blood packet I could
just start throwing right here, right now.
It’s interesting to hang out
with other comedians.
-Yes.
-Don’t you find,
'cause I've found this, that every time
you go to a party,
wherever, whatever party it is,
if there’s another comedian there,
I’m immediately going right in the corner
with the comedian and I hang out,
-and I talk the whole party.
-Yeah.
Did you see some of those scripts,
I think the Springsteen song,
and was it a Dylan song that just
were auctioned, the original writing.
Does that stuff interest you
as something... "I gotta have that"?
No, but I mean
I love looking at that stuff.
-I don't--
-I don’t know what I would do with it.
You wouldn’t buy Born to Run
for $200,000 or something?
-No.
-No. Why not?
No, because Bruce Springsteen
wouldn’t buy it for $200,000.
-He’s the one that wrote it.
-He wrote it.
Why would he ask? If he doesn’t want it,
what am I gonna do with it?
If Bruce Spring--
You're doing me again.
[laughing] I can’t, I guess.
[speaking indistinctly]
[Jerry] He doesn’t want it,
why do I want it?
[Jimmy imitating Jerry] He wrote
Born to Run. He doesn’t want it!
What am I gonna do with it?
I’m stuck with it.
It’s not who wants it, it’s who gets stuck
with it.
No, you take it!
-What I remember about meeting you at SNL.
-[Jimmy laughing]
I remember seeing you there,
when I did the show in the late '90s.
You were like a light bulb
that was just suspended in midair.
That's what you looked like.
You would just meet this guy, and you go,
"Hey, there’s no wires
holding this light bulb up.
And there’s no electricity to light it up.
How is this floating?"
"That’s Jimmy Fallon.
He’s just excited to be here."
-It’s just so...
-[both laughing]
You know what I miss?
I miss being an opening act
in front of like...
I’d go out in front of Frankie Valli,
people going, "Who is this?
We don’t want to see him,
we want to see Frankie Valli."
And you would just go,
-"What about this?
-You miss that?
What about this joke?
Why are they putting pictures
of the criminals on the walls
of the post office?
Why don’t they hang on to this guy
when they’re taking his picture?"
-[laughing] Yeah.
-And then they go,
"That is funny. That’s pretty funny."
That feeling, you’ll never have
that feeling again,
of, "Who the hell is Jimmy Fallon?
Why is Jimmy Fallon here?"
Wow, that’s a really cool--
That’s a cool old Caddie.
-[Jimmy] It's--
-Of course.
-It’s an original driver.
-Yeah, original driver.
-[laughing]
-Comes with original driver.
-Comes with the original.
-Yeah.
This is what I do. That’s my boat...
-What?
-...and that’s my little truck.
And I’m going to take you out
on it right now.
-No.
-Yeah.
And I’m going to put it
in the water myself.
[laughs]
-No way.
-Yeah, I know.
Are you kidding me?
This is unbelievable. This is awesome.
-Yeah.
-Come on.
[Jerry] This is a 1994
Land Rover Defender 90
that happens to be my personal car.
I bought it when I was doing
my TV series in LA.
I found it relaxing to get in this thing
and drive into a pile of dirt.
I love these vehicles that seem like
they want to be punished.
[horn blares]
That was the boat I wanted when I was 15.
I could never get the money together.
This is very exciting for me.
This might be the thing.
A boat, is it hard to take care of a boat?
Not a little boat like this.
And do you have to have your license
and--
No, nothing. It’s like a slide whistle.
Anyone can buy one.
This is a 13-foot Boston Whaler,
the classic boat from the classic company.
Boston Whaler began in 1958,
the boats were invented
by a guy named Dick Fischer.
It has a blue gel coat interior,
mahogany wood and a white steering wheel.
I think it’s the greatest boat
in the world. I love the logo.
I used to draw it in my schoolbooks,
just dreaming of getting one someday.
This is everything
I ever wanted in a boat.
Another absolutely indestructible vehicle.
Here they are cutting the boat in half
to prove that it’s not just a slogan,
the Boston Whaler
really is the unsinkable legend!
[chainsaw buzzing]
Oh, I love this.
I’m so excited about this.
The reason I wanted to do it,
is because I know
you, watching me...
load this boat in the water
is going to make you laugh.
["Spirit in the Sky" playing]
Norman Greenbaum, you know,
the guy who wrote "Spirit in the Sky"?
I love "Spirit in the Sky."
Great song. He goes,
"I have a home, and I have a summer home.
And I have a little boat."
I wrote one song.
It’s a Jesus song.
What’s the lyrics?
"Jesus" is in the lyrics.
-"I got a friend in Jesus."
-Yeah, "I got a friend in Jesus."
♪ Gotta have a friend in Jesus ♪
And the guy’s name is Greenbaum.
[Jimmy laughing]
I need more information.
♪ He's gonna recommend you
To the spirit in the sky ♪
♪That's where you're gonna go
When you die ♪
[Jerry] This is not
where I launch my boat.
But, uh, I'll figure it out.
Oh, this going to be interesting.
[Jerry] I don’t know where you’re going.
But this not where I go.
Yeah. I thought you had another way.
All right. I’ll turn around
with this boat.
[laughing]
That was perfectly delivered.
"All right, I’ll turn around,
with this boat."
-That’s a lot of math, a lot of angles.
-This is math and angles and geometry.
And so is comedy, by the way.
Comedy's all angles and proofs.
-Remember writing proofs?
-Yeah, of course.
That's stand-up.
You say something ridiculous,
and then you prove it to be true.
Why are the Raisin Bran people
constantly telling us about the scoops?
That’s my premise.
Now we got more scoops, bigger scoops,
longer scoops, all raisins, one flake.
We don’t like the cereal, okay?
We don’t like the cereal.
-It doesn’t matter how many scoops.
-[Jimmy laughing]
I, you know what, I think too,
I mean, I can’t believe that
we keep buying new and improved.
There’s new Mr. Clean, new and improved.
-What was the swill that we were buying?
-Swill!
When we originally invented Mr. Clean,
what was that crap?
-Nobody’s drinking Mr. Clean. Swill.
-I know, but swill.
[Jerry] When I did the speech
at the Clios, I was talking about,
I don't care that you’re lying to us
in the ad and that the product stinks,
because when I’m watching the commercial
and you say it’s great, I’m happy then.
And when I go to get it, I’m happy.
When I get it home, I’m happy,
and then I try and use it,
it doesn’t do it.
And then, I’m okay.
-‘Cause I’ll watch another commercial.
-You got a lot out of it.
Yeah, you’re doing pretty good.
You’re making us pretty happy.
Because we’re getting
moments of happiness.
That’s all I want.
I don’t want to be happy all the time.
-Yep.
-Just now and then.
That’s a lot of happy, though. Like now,
sometimes, I don’t know
what commercials are,
-‘cause now they’re all for drugs.
-Yeah.
And I don’t know
'cause they’re people being happy.
It makes you want it
because you want to be happy
You want to be like them.
They break up the drug commercials
with ads for law firms
to sue for the drugs you took last year.
That’s the only relief.
"Do you ever get thirsty?"
And you go, "I guess.
Yeah, I’ve been thirsty before.
Do I need this?
How am I living my life without this?"
"Do you ever wake up in the morning?"
Is that Batman there? Is that Rocket Man?
Who is that?
They’re filming the new Batman.
-Hey, go for it.
-All right.
Here’s the fun thing about a Land Rover.
You can go wherever you want.
It’s a Land Rover, baby.
Oh, we went in the sand.
I love how everything’s done with looks.
I love that he’s looking at us
like we’re weird.
[bleep] is going on?
The guy’s attached to ropes.
I mean, this couldn’t be a more awkward.
We’re weird?
He’s Rocket Man.
[tires screech]
This is unbelievable.
This is a great, relaxing day.
Unbelievable.
I don’t know if I could ever
do anything like this.
Now, the next thing I’m going to do
is I’m going to take off my pants.
See, I knew it was gonna get weird.
I just didn’t know how weird.
Here it is, right here.
It’s Jerry Seinfeld taking his pants off.
[Jerry] Look
at the colorful shorts I have on.
Oh, my God.
You said you liked comedy, right?
[laughing] That’s as comedy as it gets.
Never thought I’d see this.
See this is the funniest thing,
I just want footage of...
This is just great.
All right, here we go.
[Jimmy] Now what?
Exactly. Now what do I do?
I don’t understand how one man does this.
You were wondering
when he was gonna crack. This is it.
Jerry Seinfeld’s lost his mind.
Officially.
He’s a lunatic out there.
He’s wearing comedy shorts.
All right, I’ve unclamped the boat.
What do you think?
It makes you feel alive. This is great.
Your tie is caught.
All right.
[engine revving]
[theme from Flipper playing]
♪ They call him Flipper, Flipper ♪
♪ Faster than lightning ♪
♪ No one, you see ♪
♪ Is smarter than he ♪
♪ And we know
Flipper lives in a world full of wonder ♪
♪ Flying there under, under the sea ♪
[Jimmy] You know, this is unbelievable.
This is so fun.
I had no idea that
this was going to happen at all today.
This is so fun.
Come on!
What a great day!
This is the best thing ever.